addguru.in 2014-08-24

# Privacy Policy

This Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement  

is between the party using The Site  and addguru.in 

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change,

 modify or otherwise alter these terms and conditions at any time 

By using The Site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions 

You acknowledge that you have read the Terms of Use and that you accept the 

terms thereof. 

You agree to read these terms of use carefully before using The Site. 

If you do not agree to the Terms of Use, you may not access or otherwise use The 

Site. 

addguru.in  does not represent or endorse the accuracy or reliability

of any advice, opinion, statement, or other information displayed or

distributed through The Site. You acknowledge that 

any reliance upon any such , opinion, advice,

memorandum, materials , statement or information shall be at your sole risk

This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected on  

this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any

 personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described

in this privacy policy.

We reserve the right to monitor all Postings

or other materials posted on The Site and to 

remove any which we consider 

 We collect  information 

when voluntarily submitted by our visitors.

The information you provide is used to fulfill your  request.

We will share collected information for marketing purposes

Cookies And Tracking Technology 

The Site makes use cookies and other tracking technology. Cookie and tracking technologies

 are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking 

the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies 

can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot

be gathered via cookies and other tracking technology. Cookie and tracking 

information

will not be shared with third parties. 

To avail  services on 

our websites, users are required to provide

certain information for the registration process -

1 personal and business  Name 

2 Email address 

3 sex

4 Age 

5 Phone numbers 

6 E-mail address

 7 personal or business address 

8 Qualification 

9 Work Experience 

10 your occupation,and the like,interests

 11 and any other detail  provided by the user on own responsibility or on resume/   
biodata

 The Information as supplied by the 

users enables us to improve our sites and provide you

the most user-friendly experience. 

Such information will not be considered as sensitive if it is freely available and 

accessible in the public And On our Website 

Information posted on ADDGURU.IN  Will be  publicly available 

We collect and store the following personal And Business information:

1 personal and business  Name 

2 Email address 

3 

sexsexsex

4 Age 

5 Phone numbers 

6 E-mail address

 7 personal or business address 

8 Qualification 

9 Work Experience 

10 your occupation,and the like,interests

 11 and any other detail  provided by the user on own responsibility or on resume 

biodata

12 Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, 

13 Traffic to and from ADDGURU.IN  and Ad data And other information,

including users IP address and standard web log information.

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change,

 modify or otherwise alter these terms and conditions at any time

You/ users / viewers  are entirely responsible for all Content that you E- MAIL /

 FILL ANY FORM IN ADDGURU.IN 

or  in   Advertisement ,

or otherwise make available via addguru.in  Service.

By using addguru.in  Service , You/ users / viewers  are agreeing to comply with   
these Terms.

You/ users / viewers agree to abide 

guidelines for all addguru.in  services, which may change from time to time.

You/ users / viewers understand that addguru.in  does not control, and is not responsible for

Content made available through the Service, or on the advertisement  and that by 

using the Service,

you may be exposed to Content that is , indecent, misleading,offensive ,inaccurate

objectionable

The addguru.in site and Content available 

through the Service may contain 

links to other websites, which are completely

independent of addguru.in 

addguru.in  makes no representation or warranty as to the accuracy, 

authenticity  or completeness of the information contained in our advertisement .

You/ users / viewers  should make investigation you feel before proceeding with any online

or offline communication/transaction with any of these third parties advertizement .  
You/ users / viewers  agree that addguru.in shall not be responsible or liable for 

any loss 

of any sort incurred , as a result of any such dealings 

If there is a dispute between participants on this site, or between 

users and any third party, You/ users / viewers/third parties  understand and agree 

that 

addguru.in is under no obligation to become involved 

In the event that You/ users / viewers/third parties  have a dispute with one or more other third parties,You/ users / viewers/third parties

hereby release addguru.in

 Its employees, agents and successors in rights from claims,

demands and damages actual and consequential of every kind or nature,

 known or unknown, suspected and unsuspected,

addguru.in  has informed  a Privacy Policy to explain to

You/ users / viewers/third parties

how their information is collected and used

You further acknowledge and agree that addguru.in , will , 

in its sole discretion, preserve or disclose your Content, 

as well as your information, such as -

1 personal and business  Name 

2 Email address 

3 sex

4 Age 

5 Phone numbers 

6 e-mail address

 7 personal or business address 

8 Qualification 

9 Work Experience 

10 your occupation,and the ,like,interests

 11 and any other detail  provided by the user on own responsibility or on resume/ 

biodata

12 Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, 

13 Traffic to and from ADDGURU.IN  and Ad data And other information,

including users IP address and standard web log information.

addguru.in  communicates with you as a registered member through the email id and/or mobile number

that is specified in addguru.in website form or sent  e-mail addguru.in@gmail.com 

We shall use this email address and/or mobile number to send you E-mails/SMS related

 to your advertisement on our site /addguru.in ,

Updates about changes in our policies

Introduction of new services or closer of services on addguru.in .

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads 

when you visit our Web site. These companies may use 

information  

1 personal and business  Name 

2 Email address 

3 sex

4 Age 

5 Phone numbers 

6 e-mail address

 7 personal or business address 

8 Qualification 

9 Work Experience 

10 your occupation,and the ,like,interests

 11 and any other detail  provided by the user on own responsibility or on resume bio data 

12 Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, 

13 Traffic to and from ADDGURU.IN  and Ad data And other information,

including users IP address and standard web log information.

We reserve the right to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or 

materials provided by addguru.in   user

Content submitted to addguru.in  can be voted on, commented on, ranked, etc., by 

visitors to the site

stopping /Removing THE SERVICES FROM ADDGURU.IN  You/ users / 

viewers HAVE FULL RIGHT TO OPT OUT  ,

Delete your posts and/or other information , Deactivating your  SERVICES with  ADDGURU .in ,

Unsubscribe from receiving marketing communications 

You accept that The Site is provided on an  as available" basis
